dealcoupon.com 2006-12-30

# dealnews and Your Right to Privacy

dealnews.com, Inc., is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact Daniel de Grandpre via [this online contact form](http://dealnews.com/contact.html?dept=privacy) or via postal mail at 1500 Perimeter Parkway, Suite 225, Huntsville, AL 35806. If they do not receive acknowledgment of their inquiry or their inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, they should then contact TRUSTe through the [ TRUSTe Watchdog Dispute Resolution Process](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve user concerns.

The policies below are applicable to dealnews.com, dealmac.com, dealcoupon.com, dealram.com, dealcam.com, dealink.com, and other sites published by dealnews.com, Inc. (dealnews), 1500 Perimeter Parkway, Suite 225, Huntsville, AL 35806\. TRUSTe coverage extends to dealnews.com and its functional mirrors, dealmac.com, dealcoupon.com, dealram.com, dealcam.com, dealink.com.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**

dealnews respects each individual user's right to privacy. dealnews does not collect personal identifying information unless such information is specifically and knowingly provided from users during contests, surveys, sweepstakes, site registration, or use of public areas, such as a forum. From time to time, we share aggregated site traffic information with our partners and advertisers. As part of our affiliate program, we track individual user movement that is not personally identifiable. We do this to track the effectiveness of our affiliate program. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms**

If you use a bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Third Party Offers or Mailing Lists**

Users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and newsletters (ours or a third party's) if those users have opted to receive such communication. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we only send these types of communications if the user "opts-in". (Please see the Choice: Opt-In and Opt-Out section.) Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties (e.g., if we implement Third Party Mailing Lists). We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. dealnews is not responsible for any actions or policies of such outside parties.

**Choice: Opt-In and Opt-Out**

Our users are given the opportunity to "opt-in" to having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. dealnews does not supply identifying information to other companies, or use such information for its own purposes including but not limited to email newsletters, unless the user "opts-in" for such purposes by specifically allowing usage. (Identifying information must necessarily be used when notifying a user of requested information, such as email used for the alerts function, and notification of a winning entry in a contest or sweepstakes.)

Once subscribed, users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of (i.e., discontinue receiving) these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or contact us via [this online contact form](http://dealnews.com/contact.html?dept=privacy). We also offer opt-out mechanisms in the text of each email we send, and the user may contact us at the street address at the top of this page to opt-out.

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done at [mydealnews](http://dealnews.com/preferences.html?pref_view=profile) or by contacting us via [this online contact form](http://dealnews.com/contact.html?dept=privacy). 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or a legal process served on our Web site.

On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, although they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

**Security**

dealnews uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, dealnews is not responsible for any breach of security. If a dealnews user knowingly provides personal information, such as a name or email address, in a forum or other public service, that user should be aware that the information provided can be collected and used by third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of dealnews. However, at registration a user can choose whether an email is disclosed in the profile/post of the forum user.

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. dealnews will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. dealnews stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

**Cookies**

Non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of dealnews' Internet servers (i.e. log file information like IP address) or through the use of "cookies." Cookies are small text files that our site places on your computer's hard drive to recognize repeat users and facilitate the user's use of the site. Also, our cookies allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data for content improvement, targeted advertising, and marketing and promotional purposes.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). Users should be aware that dealnews cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or other third parties. Most browsers allow a user to deny cookies; however, users should note that cookies may be required to provide certain web site features.

**Third Party Advertising**

Some of the ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by LinkShare, Commision Junction, and BeFree, our Web advertising partners. Information about users' visits to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about LinkShare, Commission Junction, BeFree, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please review [LinkShare's](http://www.linkshare.com/home/privacy.shtml), [Commission Junction's](http://www.cj.com/privacy.asp), and [BeFree's](http://www.befree.com/privacy.htm) privacy policies. Please understand we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**ATTENTION KIDS**

ATTENTION KIDS: No information should be submitted to dealnews by children under 18 years of age without their parent's or guardian's consent. dealnews does not monitor the age of its user audience.

dealnews reserves the right to change this policy at any time by posting notice of the existence of a new privacy statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
